Guide to the Anson Phelps Stokes Autograph Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- CORRESPONDENCE, 1713-1958; Series I
  - Maltby, Isaac (1767-1819), 1803 July 15 (Box 6, Folder 363)
    ALS to Increase Cooke
  - Mansfield, Jared (1759-1830), 1819 March 29 (Box 6, Folder 364)
    ALS to "Dear Sir"; biographical notes
  - Marsh, James (1794-1842), 1814 March 3 (Box 6, Folder 365)
    ALS to John Cessna
  - Marsh, Othniel Charles (1831-1899), 1873 June 4, 1888 May 15, 1896 June 9 (Box 6, Folder 366)
    ALS (copy) to President Porter
    ALS to Fred Brown
    ALS to F. B. Dexter
  - Mason, Ebenezer Porter (1819-1840), Undated (Box 6, Folder 367)
    Page of astronomical calculations; biographical notes
  - Mason, Jeremiah (1768-1848), 1814 February 21, 1821 June 1 (Box 6, Folder 368)
    ALS to Col. Robert Means
    ALS to William Burleigh
  - Masters, Josiah (1763-1822), 1819 November 29 (Box 6, Folder 369)
    ALS to David Galispie (sic)
  - Mather, Eleazar (1716-1798), 1777 May 10 (Box 6, Folder 370)
    ALS to Dudley Saltonstall; also portrait
  - Meigs, Henry (1782-1861), 1823 April 4 (Box 6, Folder 371)
    ALS to Asbury Dickins
  - Meigs, Josiah (1757-1822), 1812 August 5 (Box 6, Folder 372)
    ALS to Thomas Jefferson
  - Meigs, Return Jonathan (1764-1825), 1809 June 26 (Box 6, Folder 373)
    ALS to George Tod-
  - Miller, Asher (1753-1821), 1799 April 20 (Box 6, Folder 374)
    ALS to the publishers of the Annual Repositer
  - Mills, Isaac (1767-1843), 1810 January 2 (Box 6, Folder 375)
    ALS to I. Beers
  - Minor, William Thomas (1815-1889), 1884 August 13 (Box 6, Folder 376)
    ALS to "My Dear Young Lady"
  - Mitchell, Donald Grant (1822-1908), 1865 October 27, 1902 December 22 (Box 6, Folder 377)
    ALS to Pres. T. Dwight Woolsey
  - Mitchell, Stephen Mix (1743-1835), 1775 September 2 (Box 6, Folder 378)
    Receipted bill signed for articles bought from Mr. Lockwood
    also biographical notes and picture
  - Mix, Timothy (1711-1779), 1763 April 20 (Box 6, Folder 379)
    ADS a deed to Nathan Beers
  - Morgan, Christopher (1808-1877), 1849 July 16 (Box 6, Folder 380)
    ALS to H. Martindale
  - Morgan, John (1753-1842), 1832 January 2 (Box 6, Folder 381)
    Autograph: written
  - Moore, George Foot (1851-1931), 1913 June 25 (Box 6, Folder 382)
  - Morris, Lewis (1726-1798), 1778 April 4 (Box 6, Folder 383)
    Signed receipt of money due him as a member of New York Senate; also portrait
  - Morris, Luzon Burritt (1827-1895), 1892 (Box 6, Folder 384)
    MSS portion of draft of inaugural address signed
  - Morris, Richard (1730-1810), 1792 July 19 (Box 6, Folder 385)
    ALS to Robert Morris
  - Morse, Jedidiah (1761-1826), 1821 July 3 (Box 6, Folder 386)
    ADS with Howe and Spalding (publishers)
    on reverse side ANS to Howe and Spalding
  - Morse, Richard Cary (1841-1926), 1896 May 4, 1908 September 18 (Box 6, Folder 387)
    also a souvenir menu with portrait and guest signatures
  - Morse, Samuel Finley Breese (1791-1872), 1867 April 12, 1807 January 19 (Box 6, Folder 388)
    ALS to E.H. Chaplin (on reverse side is copy by Morse of Chaplin's letter to him 1867 Jan 27)
    "Books necessary to study to enter Sophomore Year" addressed to E. Abbot
  - Moseley, William Abbot (1799-1873), 1841 March 9 (Box 6, Folder 389)
  - Mulford, Rev. Elisha (1833-1885), 1870 July 5 (Box 6, Folder 390)
    ALS to Theodore Thornton Munger
  - Mumford, Paul (1734-1805), 1784 October 13 (Box 6, Folder 391)
    Order to pay Paul Mumford endorsed
  - Munger, Rev. Theodore Thornton (1830-1910), 1904 December 12, undated (Box 6, Folder 392)
  - Nelson, Rensselaer Russell (1826-1904), 1875 March 30 (Box 6, Folder 393)
  - Nettleton, Rev. Asabel (1783-1844) (Box 6, Folder 394)
  - Nevins, Rev. William (1797-1835), Undated (Box 6, Folder 395)
    Ms. Sermon on Corinthians 1:30 (no. 654); biographical notes.
  - Newberry, Roger (1706-1741), 1736 October 4 (Box 6, Folder 396)
    ADS deed on which Newberry's name appears
  - Newlands, Francis Griffith (1848-1917), 1865 September 20 (Box 6, Folder 397)
    Autograph on printed form
  - Newton, Hubert Anson (1830-1896), 1855 November 27 (Box 6, Folder 398)
    4 pages of Diary; biographical notes; portrait
  - Nichols, Alfred Bull (1852-1913), 1878 August 25 (Box 6, Folder 399)
    ALS to E. E. Salisbury [Transferred to Salisbury Family Papers}
  - Noble, John Willock (1831-1912), 1891 May 5, 1911 July 8 (Box 6, Folder 400)
    ALS to T. T. Munger [Transferred to Theodore Thornton Munger Papers]
  - North, Simeon (1802-1884) (Box 6, Folder 401)
    ALS to Rev. H. Darling
  - Northrop, Birdsey Grant (1818-1898), 1873 May 6 (Box 6, Folder 402)
    ALS to Prof. W. Mathews; obituary clipping
  - Norton, John Pitkin (1822-1852), 1850 March 2 (Box 6, Folder 403)
    Autograph; biographical notes; portrait
  - Oakley, Thomas Jackson (1783-1857), 1819 August 24 (Box 6, Folder 404)
    ALS to D. Gillespie
  - Ogden, David (1707-1798), 1761 April 6, 1797 September 12 (Box 6, Folder 405)
    ALS to Garrit Rappilee (sic)
    PDS disposition to a Bill of Landing
  - Olcott, Simeon (1735-1815), Undated (Box 6, Folder 406)
    ANS to the Vice President accepting a dinner invitation
  - Olmstead, Hawley (1793-1868), 1862 August 6 (Box 6, Folder 407)
    [Transferred to Woolsey Family Papers]
  - Olmsted, Denison (1791-1859), 1841 September 20, undated (Box 6, Folder 408)
    ALS to D. Appleton
    Ms. outlines of lectures on meteorology given at Yale College; biographical notes; portrait
  - Olmsted, Frederick Law (1822-1903), 1858 October 14 (Box 6, Folder 409)
    ALS to the editor of the "Atlantic Monthly"
  - Osborne, Thomas Burr (1798-1869), 1841 December 22 (Box 6, Folder 410)
    ALS to the Secretary of the Navy
  - Owen, Allen Ferdinand (1816-1865), 1851 March 3 (Box 6, Folder 411)
    ALS to William A. Graham
  - Packard, Alpheus Spring (1839-1905), 1870 January 20 (Box 6, Folder 412)
    ALS to Dr. Ballard
  - Palmer, Ray (1808-1887), 1869 December 8 (Box 6, Folder 413)
    ALS to Rev. Walter S. Alexander; portrait
  - Park, Edwards Amasa (1808-1900), Undated (Box 6, Folder 414)
    ANS to Mr. Alexander
  - Parker, Edward Griffin (1825-1868), 1865 December 2 (Box 6, Folder 415)
    ALS to B. P. Poore
  - Parker, Horatio I. (n.y.), 1917 February 24 (Box 6, Folder 416)
    TLS to A. P. Stokes
  - Parker, Rev. Peter (1804-1888), 1841 February 15, 1841 March 5, 1868 December 5 (Box 6, Folder 417)
    2 ALS to Professor Edward Salisbury [Transferred to Salisbury Family Papers]
    ALS to L. J. Cist (also negative photostat)
  - Parsons, Jonathan (1705-1776), 1766 November 27 (Box 6, Folder 418)
    Sermon preached on Luke 10: 5
  - Parsons, Lewis Baldwin (1818-1906), 1906 July 28 (Box 6, Folder 419)
    ALS to Rev. Dr. Munger
  - Partridge, Sidney Catlin (1857-1930), (1910) June 21 (Box 6, Folder 420)
    ALS to A.F. Stokes
  - Paterson, Major General John (1744-1808), 1787 January 29 (Box 7, Folder 421)
    ALS to Maj. Gen. Lincoln
  - Peck, Tracy (1838-1921), 1898 March 28 (Box 7, Folder 422)
  - Peet, Rev. Stephen (1795-1855), 1841 March 15 (Box 7, Folder 423)
    ALS to Dexter Clary
  - Percival, James Gates (1795-1855), 1818 September 20, undated, undated (Box 7, Folder 424)
    MS signed of a poem "Elegy"
    "Lines Addressed to a Young Lady…"
    some loose pages from his notebook
  - Perit, Peletiah (1785-1864), 1848 December 20 (Box 7, Folder 425)
    ALS to Col. Aspinwall
  - Perrin, Bernadotte (1847-1920), 1904 February 17 (Box 7, Folder 426)
  - Peters, John Andrew (1822-1904), 1863 February 9 (Box 7, Folder 427)
  - Peters, Samuel (Rev.) (1735-1826), 1804 March 31 (Box 7, Folder 428)
    ALS to Miss Harriot D. Jarvis
  - Phelps, Alfred, 1833 June 7 (Box 7, Folder 429)
    ALS to George Kirkum
  - Phelps, Edward John (1822-1900), Undated (Box 7, Folder 430)
    ALS to Prof. Dexter
  - Phelps, Elisha (1779-1847), 1826 March 23 (Box 7, Folder 431)
  - Phelps, Samuel Shethar(1793-1855), 1842 April 14 (Box 7, Folder 432)
    ALS to W. Chapman Esq.
    portrait
  - Phelps, William Lyon (1865-1943), 1908 January 6 (Box 7, Folder 433)
  - Phelps, William Walter (1839-1894), 1887 April 9 (Box 7, Folder 434)
    ALS to Rossiter Johnson
  - Phillips, Andrew Wheeler (1844-1915), 1907 November 24 (Box 7, Folder 435)
  - Pierpont, John (1785-1866), 1856 December 1 (Box 7, Folder 436)
    ALS to Bernard Capen; also biographical notes and portrait
  - Pierrepont, Edwards (1817-1892), 1869 October 21 (Box 7, Folder 437)
    ALS to Pres. and Atty. General of United States [Transferred to Edwards Pierrepont Papers]
    also biographical notes
  - Pitkin, Timothy (1766-1847), 1819 July 15 (Box 7, Folder 438)
  - Polk, Trusten (1811-1876), 1860 June 25 (Box 7, Folder 439)
    ALS to "Dear Reynolds"
  - Pomeroy, Benjamin (1704-1784), 1770 December 16 (Box 7, Folder 440)
    Manuscript notes for sermon
  - Poole, William Frederick (1821-1894), 1881 October 21 (Box 7, Folder 441)
    ALS to L.E. Jones; also biographical notes and portrait
  - Porter, Frank Chamberlain (1859-), 1908 January 5 (Box 7, Folder 442)
  - Porter, Noah (1811-1892), 1857 June 1, 1870 September 5 (Box 7, Folder 443)
    ALS to Prof. Francis Lieber
    ALS to "My Dear Friend"
  - Porter, Peter Buell (1773-1844), 1828 July 22 (Box 7, Folder 444)
    ALS to Col. William J. Duane; also biographical notes and portrait
  - Prout, John (1689-1776), 1758 September 27 (Box 7, Folder 445)
    DS: deed acknowledged before John Prout
  - Prudden, Nehemiah (1749-1815), 1784 August 31 (Box 7, Folder 446)
  - Putnam, James Osborne (1818-1903), n.y. March 25 (Box 7, Folder 447)
    ALS to Levi Morton
  - Quint, Alonzo Hall (1828-1896), 1870 April 12 (Box 7, Folder 448)
  - Reed, John (Rev.) (1751-1831), Undated (Box 7, Folder 449)
    Manuscript Sermon
  - Remington, Frederic (1861-1909), 1896 April 6 (Box 7, Folder 450)
    ALS to Julian Ralph; also portrait
  - Reynolds, James Bronson (1861-1924), 1898 January 15 (Box 7, Folder 451)
  - Rice, James Clay (1829-1864), 1862 November 28 (Box 7, Folder 452)
    ALS to Capt. A Cleghorn; also portrait
  - Richards, William Rogers (1853-1910), 1904 February 22 (Box 7, Folder 453)
  - Ripley, William Brintnall (1768-1822), 1813 October 23 (Box 7, Folder 454)
    ALS to Messrs. Howe and Deforest
  - Robbins, Ammi Ruhamah (1740-1813), 1808 October 6 (Box 7, Folder 455)
    ALS to Benjamin Tallmadge
  - Robbins, Asher (1761-1845), 1842 February 12 (Box 7, Folder 456)
    ALS to Mr. Upshur
  - Robbins, Chandler (1738-1799), Undated (Box 7, Folder 457)
  - Robbins, Thomas (Rev.) (1777-1856), 1835 September 23 (Box 7, Folder 458)
    ALS to Messrs. Hezekiah Howe & Co.
  - Robertson, Charles Franklin, Rt. Rev. (1835-1886), 1893 August 27 (Box 7, Folder 459)
    ALS to the Rev. Mr. Berkeley
  - Robertson, John Brownlee (1809-1892), 1848 April 20 (Box 7, Folder 460)
    ALS to George Warren
  - Roberts, Ellis Henry (1827-1918), 1871 April 27 (Box 7, Folder 461)
    ALS to the publishers of the Globe
  - Robinson, William Erigena (1814-1892), 1848 October 4 (Box 7, Folder 462)
    ALS to Messrs. Blair and Rives; also portrait
  - Rockwell, John Arnold (1803-1861), 1848 December 20 (Box 7, Folder 463)
  - Rockwell, Julius (1805-1888), 1834 December 20 (Box 7, Folder 464)
    ALS to Mr. Briggs
  - Ruggles, Samuel Bulkley (1800-1881), 1823 March 10 (Box 7, Folder 465)
    ALS (copy) to Gen. Talmadge
  - Russell, William Huntington (1809-1885), 1870 July 3 (Box 7, Folder 466)
    Note of recommendation
  - Rutledge, Rev. Edward (1797-1832), 1825 November 25 (Box 7, Folder 467)
    ALS to Messrs. A. Binninger and Son
  - Salisbury, Edward Elbridge (1814-1901), 1856 September 14 (Box 7, Folder 468)
    ALS and receipt to Pres. T.D. Woolsey; also portrait
  - Saltonstall, Gurdon (1666-1724), 1713 May 7 (Box 7, Folder 469)
    ALS to Gov. Dudley; also portrait
  - Sampson, Ezra, Undated (Box 7, Folder 470)
    Transcript of passage about Ezra Sampson
  - Sanders, Frank Knight (1861-1933), 1898(?) April 5 (Box 7, Folder 471)
  - Schuyler, Eugene (1840-1890), 1870 July 23/August 4, 1877 December 19 (Box 7, Folder 472)
    ALS to M.D.
    PDS
    also biographical notes and Portrait
  - Schwab, John Christopher (1865-1916), 1898 February 10 (Box 7, Folder 473)
  - Scott, John Morin (1730-1784), 1767 January 14 (Box 7, Folder 474)
    ADS
  - Seabury, Bishop Samuel (1729-1796), 1785 October 18, 1913 August 24 (Box 7, Folder 475)
    DS
    ALS to W.J. Seabury to A.P. Stokes
  - Seabury, Warren Bartlett (1877-1907), 1904(i.e.1905)January 4 (Box 7, Folder 476)
  - Sedgwick, Theodore (1746-1813), (1801)September 6 (Box 7, Folder 477)
    ALS to Thomas Darling; also biographical notes and portrait
  - Sedgwick, Theodore (1780-1839), 1829 October 23 (Box 7, Folder 478)
    ALS to Messrs. Carey, Lea & Carey
  - Seeley, John Edward (1810-1875), 1871 June 28 (Box 7, Folder 479)
    ALS to F &G Rives and Geo. A Beeleg(?)
  - Sergeant, Rev. John (1710-1749), Undated (Box 7, Folder 480)
    ALS to Rev. Stephen Williams
    also biographical notes and photo of his house
  - Sergeant, John (1747-1824), 177? October 16 (Box 7, Folder 481)
    ALS to Eleazar Wheelock (neg. photostat)
  - Sewall, Judge .Samuel (1652-1730), Undated (Box 7, Folder 482)
    Receipt signed; also portrait and biographical notes
  - Seymour, David Lowrey (1803-1867), 1848 January 21 (Box 7, Folder 483)
    ALS to Dr. Thomas P. Jones
  - Seymour, Horatio (1778-1857), 1841 April 30 (Box 7, Folder 484)
    ALS to Pres. Tyler
  - Seymour, Origen Storrs (1804-1881), 1871 July 3 (Box 7, Folder 485)
    ALS to "My Dear Sir"; also portrait
  - Seymour, Thomas (1734/5-1829), Undated (Box 7, Folder 486)
    Autograph note to Gov. Huntington
  - Shedd, William Greenough Thayer (1820-1894), 1852 November 23 (Box 7, Folder 487)
  - Shepard, Samuel (1772-1846), 1833 February 18 (Box 7, Folder 488)
    Autograph; also biographical notes
  - Sherman, Henry (1808-1879), 1859 February 16 (Box 7, Folder 489)
    ALS to W.H. Seward
  - Sherman, John (1772-1828), Undated (Box 7, Folder 490)
    MS Sermon on I Thessalonians 5.21 (20 pages)
  - Sherman, Roger (1721-1793), 1774 December 26 (Box 7, Folder 491)
    Summons for John Eliot to appear in court
  - Sherman, Roger Minott (1773-1844), 1835 August 5 (Box 7, Folder 492)
    ALS to Samuel Hitchcock; also portrait
  - Sherman, Samuel (1704-1769), 1763 September 20 (Box 7, Folder 493)
    Printed DS being a deed for land
    in New Haven witnessed by Samuel Sherman
  - Shiras, George (1832-1924), 1896 April 6 (Box 7, Folder 494)
    ALS to Belmont Perry
  - Shorter, Eli Simms (1823-1879), 1859 December 28 (Box 7, Folder 495)
    ALS to Globe Office
  - Sill, Edward Rowland (1841-1887), 1886 (Box 7, Folder 496)
    ALS to Dr. Martin Kellogg; also portrait
  - Sill, Major Richard (1775-1790), 1785 May 7 (Box 7, Folder 497)
    ALS to Aaron Burr
  - Silliman, Benjamin (1779-1864), 1828 June 7, 1842 August 17, 1862 July 25 (Box 8, Folder 498)
    ALS to Prof. Parker Cleavland (neg. photostat) [Transferred to Silliman Family Papers]
    MSS draft of address given before the Association of the Alumni [Transferred to Silliman Family Papers]
    ALS to T.D. Woolsey
  - Silliman, Benjamin II (1816-1885), 1877 April 1, 1879 June 9 (Box 8, Folder 499)
    ALS to Prof. Salisbury
    [All items transferred to Salisbury Family Papers]
  - Silliman, Benjamin Douglas (1805-1901), 1829 March 18 (Box 8, Folder 500)
  - Slidell, Thomas (1807-1864), 1848 December 12 (Box 8, Folder 501)
    ALS to Persifor E. Smith
  - Smalley, George Washburn (1833-1916), 1868 June 30 (Box 8, Folder 502)
    ALS to Mr. Anderson
  - Smith, Ashbel (1805-1886), 1851 March 21 (Box 8, Folder 503)
  - Smith, Rev. Eli, 1852 September 13 (Box 8, Folder 504)
    ALS to Dr. Edward Robinson; also biographical notes and portrait
  - Smith, Israel (1779-1810), 1790 February ? (Box 8, Folder 505)
    ANS receipt for promissory note from D. Page
  - Smith, Joel Sumner (1830-1903), 1893 May 10 (Box 8, Folder 506)
    Receipt for $10.00 for the Phi Beta Kappa fund
    [Transferred to Joel Sumner Smith Papers]
  - Smith, John Cotton (1765-1845), 1815 July 15 (Box 8, Folder 507)
    ALS to Gen. Burbeck
  - Smith, John Cotton (1810-1879), 1845 April 23 (Box 8, Folder 508)
    ALS to Robert J. Walker
  - Smith, Junius (Class of 1802) (1780-1853), 1807 March 10 (Box 8, Folder 509)
    ALS to his parents; also biographical notes and portrait
  - Smith, Truman, 1847 July 29 (Box 8, Folder 510)
    ALS to "My Dear Sir"
  - Smith, William (1697-1769), 1734 May 1 (Box 8, Folder 511)
    ADS suit for debt brought before Smith
  - Smith, William (1728-1793), C. 1760 (Box 8, Folder 512)
    ALS to John Tabor Kempe; also biographical notes and portrait
  - Smyth, Newman (1843-1925), 1907 November 3 (Box 8, Folder 513)
  - Spalding, Rufus Paine (1798-1886), 1848 November 23 (Box 8, Folder 514)
    ALS to Robert F. Paine
  - Sprague, Homer Baxter (1829-1918), 1911 January 14, 1911 February 7, 1870 June 2 (Box 8, Folder 515)
    ALS to Charles Mumford
  - Sprague, Rev. William Buell (1795-1876), 1836 September 7 (Box 8, Folder 516)
    ALS to Dawson Turner
  - Springs, Rev. Gardiner (1785-1873), 1823 March 20 (Box 8, Folder 517)
    ALS to Edward D. Griffin
  - Sproat, Rev. James (1722-1793), 1793 October 10 (Box 8, Folder 518)
    ALS to John Sproat
  - Stanley, Anthony Dummond (1810-1853), 1843 July 10 (Box 8, Folder 519)
    ANS letter of recommendation
  - Stedman, Edmund Clarence (1833-1908), Undated, 1881 May 8, 1888 November 21 (Box 8, Folder 520)
    MS signed of a poem (illegible and faded)
    ALS to Jenny Croly
    ALS to James Kenyon
  - Steele, Eliphalet (1742-1817), 1783 June 8 (Box 8, Folder 521)
  - Sterling, Micah (1784-1844), 1822 January 12 (Box 8, Folder 522)
    ALS to Mr. Edwards
  - Stetson, Charles (1801-1883), 1880 March 5 (Box 8, Folder 523)
    ALS to Mr. Rives
  - Stevens, Dr. Alexander Hodgdon (1789-1869), 1847 March 26 (Box 8, Folder 524)
    ALS to Prof. S.H. Dickson; also biographical notes and portrait
  - Stevens, Henry (1819-1886), 1852 June 8, 1861 April 6 (Box 8, Folder 525)
    ALS to Collector of Customs New York
    ALS to Simon Stevens
    [All items transferred to Henry Stevens Papers]
  - Stevens, John Austin (1795-1874), 1840 February 22 (Box 8, Folder 526)
  - Stewart, William Morris (1827-1909), 1865 September 10 (Box 8, Folder 527)
  - Stiles, Abel (1709-1783), 1741 July 29, 1763 January 2 and 1768 January 20 (Box 8, Folder 528)
    Sermon 21 on Gal. 6.15
  - Stiles, Ezra (1727-1795), 1782 January 20, 1783 February 25, 1787 February 26 (Box 8, Folder 529)
    ALS (neg. photostat) to Rev.
    Hitchcock
    ALS to Gen. Greene
    ALS to Prof. Williams
  - Stillé, Charles Janeway (1819-1899), 1875 May 14 (Box 8, Folder 530)
    ALS to E.C. Mitchell; also biographical notes and portrait
  - Stokes, Rev. Anson Phelps (1874-1958), 1958 August 14 (Box 8, Folder 531)
    Obituary
  - Storrs, Henry Randolph (1787-1837), 1818 March 16 (Box 8, Folder 532)
    ALS to T. Gales
  - Storrs, William Lucius (1795-1861), 1848 January 1 (Box 8, Folder 533)
    ALS to Messrs. Gales and Seaton; also biographical notes
  - Strong, Cyprian (1743-1811), Undated (Box 8, Folder 534)
    Sermon on Hebrews 4.2 signed
  - Strong, Jedidiah (1738-1802), 1780 July 3 (Box 8, Folder 535)
    ADS Resolution of Governor and Council of Safety receipted
  - Strong, Rev. Nathan (1748-1816), Undated (Box 8, Folder 536)
    Sermon on John 13.35; also biographical notes
  - Strong, Theodore (1790-1867), 1844 August 31 (Box 8, Folder 537)
    ALS to M.V.L. McClelland; also biographical notes
  - Strong, William (1808-1895), 1866 May 7 (Box 8, Folder 538)
    ALS to his brother and sister and Elizabeth
  - Stuart, Moses (1780-1852), 1830 March 16 (Box 8, Folder 539)
    ALS to Samuel Elliott; also biographical notes and portrait
  - Sturges, Jonathan (1740-1819), 1788 January 2 (Box 8, Folder 540)
    Printed DS summons issued by J. Sturges
  - Sullivan, John Langdon (1777-1865), 1836 March 2 (Box 8, Folder 541)
    ALS to Luther Bradish
  - Sullivant, William Starling, (1803-1873), 1857 February 17 (Box 8, Folder 542)
    ALS to D. C. Eaton Esq. [Transferred to Daniel Cady Eaton Papers]
  - Sumner, William Graham, 1900 July 28 (Box 8, Folder 543)
    ALS to Professor Albert G. Keller
  - Swayne, Wager (1834-1902), 1870 January 7 (Box 8, Folder 544)
    ALS to Thomas H. Talbot
  - Swift, George (ca. 1796-1845), 1832 August 29 (Box 8, Folder 545)
    ALS to Clerk of Court of Common Pleas
  - Swift, Job (1743-1804), Undated (Box 8, Folder 546)
    Sermon on Daniel 5:23
  - Swift, Zephaniah (1759-1823), 1798 March 15 (Box 8, Folder 547)
    ALS to Ephraim Root
    2 photographs of his tomb
  - Taft, Alphonso (1810-1891), 1877 October 17 (Box 8, Folder 548)
    ALS to Robert G. Ingersoll
  - Taft, William Howard (1857-1930), 1909 November 21, 1910 January 10 (Box 8, Folder 549)
    TLS to A. P. Stokes (negative photostat)
  - Tallmadge, Benjamin (1754-1835), 1808 September 19, 1783 June 29 (Box 8, Folder 550)
    ALS to Mr. Bacon
    ALS to Peter Colt Esq.; portrait
  - Tallmadge, Frederick Augustus (1792-1869), 1843 January 28 (Box 8, Folder 551)
    ALS to Robert Tyler
  - Tallmadge, Matthias Burnet (1774-1819), 1813 October 25 (Box 8, Folder 552)
    ALS to William P. Van Ness
  - Taylor, Nathaniel William (1786-1858), 1850 April 12, 1809 November 25 (Box 8, Folder 553)
    ALS to Stephen Van Rensselaer
  - Taylor, Richard (1826-1879), 1862 March 14 (Box 8, Folder 554)
    ALS to Gen. Richard Stoddard Ewell
  - Terry, Alfred Howe (1827-1890), 1873 September 21 (Box 9, Folder 555)
    ALS to General W.W. Belknap
  - Thacher, Thomas (1850-1919), 1899 March 28 (Box 9, Folder 556)
  - Thacher, Thomas Anthony (1815-1886), 1864 December 29 (Box 9, Folder 557)
    ALS to Samuel B.Ruggles; also portrait
  - Thompson, Joseph Parrish (1819-1879) (Box 9, Folder 558)
  - Thurston, John Lawrence (1874-1904) (Box 9, Folder 559)
  - Tilden, Samuel Jones (1814-1886), 1853 February 1, 1866 January 7 (Box 9, Folder 560)
    ALS to G.W. Newel
    ALS to H.A. Smythe
  - Tod, George (1773-1841), 1814 November 29 (Box 9, Folder 561)
    Military certificate signed
    Legal note attached signed
  - Todd, John (1800-1873), 1845 December 8 (Box 9, Folder 562)
    ALS to Alexander Hyde
  - Todd, Jonathan (1713-1791), Undated (Box 9, Folder 563)
    Manuscript sermon
  - Tomlinson, Gideon (1780-1854), 1832 January 17 (Box 9, Folder 564)
    ALS to Gen. (Hezekiah) Howe
  - Townsend, William Kneeland (1848-1907), Undated (Box 9, Folder 565)
  - Tracy, Uriah (1755-1807), 1799 October 10 (Box 9, Folder 566)
    ALS to Gen. Huntington
  - Treadwell, John (1745-1823), 1810 May 8, 1810 November 6 (Box 9, Folder 567)
    ALS to Harry Croswell
  - Trumbull, Benjamin (1735-1820), 1778 April 2 (Box 9, Folder 568)
    MS Sermon Luke XII 35-40; also portrait
  - Trumbull, James Hammond(1821-1897), 1878 April 16, 1879 February 13 (Box 9, Folder 569)
    ALS to Prof. Edward E. Salisbury
    ALS to Prof. Edward E. Salisbury (on neg. photostat)
  - Trumbull, John (1750-1831), 1772 January 8 (Box 9, Folder 570)
    ALS to Silas Deane
  - Trumbull, John (1756-1843), 1818 July 28 (Box 9, Folder 571)
    ALS to Capt. Newcomb
  - Trumbull, Jonathan (1710-1785), 1777 February 21 (Box 9, Folder 572)
    ALS to Capt. Jared Tracy
  - Trumbull, Joseph (1782-1861), 1803 May 7 (Box 9, Folder 573)
    ALS to Samuel Huntington
  - Turner, Jonathan (Box 9, Folder 574)
    Article about J. Turner in the Illinois State Historical Society Journal
  - Twichell, Joseph Hopkins (1838-1918), n.y. December 14 (Box 9, Folder 575)
  - Twining, Alexander Catlin (1801-1884), 1853 February 17 (Box 9, Folder 576)
    ALS to his daughter Eliza
  - Tyler, Bennet (1783-1858), 1817 December 13 (Box 9, Folder 577)
    Autograph note to "Dear Sir"